Some secrets are too powerful to hide.
Finding Altamira is a drama, history film directed by Hugh Hudson.
The story of nine-year old Maria and her father Marcelino who, in 1879, found the
first pre-historic cave paintings at the now world famous Altamira cave.
Marcelino, played by Antonio Banderas.
Conchita, played by Golshifteh Farahani.
Monseñor, played by Rupert Everett.
Paul Ratier, played by Pierre Niney.
De los Ríos, played by Henry Goodman.
Abbé Breuil, played by Tristán Ulloa.
Finding Altamira (released as Altamira in Spain) is a 2016 Spanish biographical
drama film starring Antonio Banderas, and directed by Hugh Hudson.
It was Hudson's first fiction film as director since I Dreamed of Africa in 2000,
although he wrote the screenplay for the 2014 fictional film, The Journey Home.
It was his final film before his death in 2023.
The film explores themes of spain, cave, discovery, altamira.
The tone is emotional.